//BreakingBad question and answer data sore//
const STORE = [
{
question: "Hyper Text Markup Language Stand For?",
ans1: 'Javascript',
ans2: 'XML',
ans3: 'HTML',
ans4: 'CSS',

correctAnswer: 'HTML',
},
{
question: 'Chandler is a teacher of what high school subject?',
ans1: 'Chemistry',
ans2: 'Biology',
ans3: 'Physics',
ans4: 'Geology',

correctAnswer: 'Chemistry',
},
{
question: "Which language is used for styling web pages?",
ans1: 'HTML',
ans2: 'CSS',
ans3: 'Java',
ans4: 'XML',

correctAnswer: 'CSS',
},
{
question: "Which is not a JavaScript Framework?",
ans1: 'Javascript',
ans2: 'ReactJS',
ans3: 'Python',
ans4: 'Nodejs',

correctAnswer: 'Python',
},
{
question: "What's the name of the fried chicken restaurant owned by Gus?",
ans1: 'Pollos',
ans2: 'Pollo Feliz',
ans3: 'Delicioso Pollo',
ans4: 'Amigos de Pollo',

correctAnswer: 'Pollos',
},
{
question: 'Which is used for Connect To Database?',
ans1: 'HTML',
ans2: 'CSS',
ans3: 'XML',
ans4: 'PHP',

correctAnswer: 'PHP',
},
{
question: 'Webdevtrick.com is about..',
ans1: 'Web Design',
ans2: 'Graphic Design',
ans3: 'SEO',
ans4: 'ALL',

correctAnswer: 'ALL',
},
{
question: 'What is Python?',
ans1: 'Snake',
ans2: 'Bird',
ans3: 'Programming Language',
ans4:'Animal',
correctAnswer: 'Programming Language',
},
{
question: 'What is the best framework?',
ans1: 'Reactjs',
ans2: 'Angularjs',
ans3: 'Vuejs',
ans4: 'ALL',

correctAnswer: 'ALL',
},
{
question: 'What is the best Language to learn?',
ans1: 'Python',
ans2: 'Java',
ans3: 'C',
ans4: 'ALL',

correctAnswer: 'ALL',
}
];













